webmasterworld.com 2019-09-14

# Help : - WebmasterWorld

> **Privacy Statement for Webmaster World**
> 
> Webmaster World is owned and operated by [WebmasterWorld and DevShed, LLC.](http://www.webmasterworld.com/). 
> 
> WebmasterWorld and DevShed, LLC. has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. 
> 
> The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: webmasterworld.com 
> 
> We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address may be used to gather broad demographic information. 
> 
> This site contains links to other sites. **WebmasterWorld and DevShed, LLC.** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 
> 
> We may use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we may use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. 
> 
> ## Public Forums
> 
> This site may make chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 
> 
> ## Security 
> 
> This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. 
> 
> ## Electronic Mail
> 
> By providing their email address when signing up for this site, users authorize us to send them site notifications, newsletters, or other information via email from time to time. Users may remove themselves from such services at their discretion. Any email sent to a list will include directions for how a user may remove himself or herself from the list. 
> 
> ## Children's Guidelines
> 
> This web site meets the guidelines of [TRUSTe's](http://www.truste.org/) Children's program. 
> 
>   1. We do NOT collect online contact information without prior parental consent or parental notification, which will include an opportunity for the parent to prevent use of the information and participation in the activity. Without prior parental consent, online information will only be used to respond directly to the child's request and will not be used for other purposes without prior parental consent. 
>   2. We do NOT collect personally identifiable offline contact information without prior parental consent. 
>   3. We do NOT distribute to third parties any personally identifiable information with out prior parental consent. 
>   4. We do NOT give the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information without prior parental consent. 
>   5. We do NOT entice by the prospect of a special game, prize or other activity, to divulge more information than is needed to participate in the activity. 
> 

> 
> ## Contacting the Web Site
> 
> If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: 
>     
>     
>      Webmaster World, c/o/ Pubcon Inc.
>      2504 Dana Cove STE A
>      Austin TX 78746
>      http://www.webmasterworld.come-mail: engine at webmasterworld.com
>
